# THY **NGUYEN**FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Ho Chi Minh · 0328618887 · 01/01/1996 thuthy0101@gmail.com · https://thynguyen96.github.io

Main area of my expertise is front end development, and everything related with web development. HTML, CSS, JS, Bootstrap, jQuery, building single page web applications with Angular. Currently, I work as a web developer, experienced with frontend development with Angular and backend development with PHP and framework like Yii. I also have experience working with database like MySQL.

## SKILL

Frontend: Angular /HTML/CSS/Bootstrap

• Backend: PHP/Yii Framework.

• Others: Git/MySQL.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **DEC 2020 - PRESENT**

# FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPER, CÔNG TY CÔNG NGHỆ GIÁO DỤC VIE EDU

- Developing website and mobile application for teaching and taking online tests using Angular, PHP (Yii Framework), MySQL.
- Frontend web: https://eduvietnam.vn/

#### **JUN 2020 - DEC 2020**

## **FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPER, SGIS**

- Developing Educational and Employee Management website based on business and requirements using Angular, PHP, MySQL, Yii Framework
- Creating a RESTful API endpoint.
- Developing front end responsive websites.
- Feature development

#### JUN 2018 - JUN 2020

## **SOFTWARE ENGINEER, TMA SOLUTIONS**

- Building Plugins/Extensions of the software system for managing network devices.
- Writing and executing test scripts for each development unit as well as a high-level test
- Training newcomers in terms of being used to the project and essential technologies.
- Discussing with the offshore team by stand-up daily meeting (SCRUM) and email.
- Develop new feature.
- Bug fixing.

#### MAR 2020 - MAY 2020

# FRONTEND DEVELOPER, FREELANCER

- Developing real estate brokerage website using ReactJS, NextJS, GraphQL (Apollo), Redux (Thunk and Saga).
- Developing front end responsive websites.

## JUN 2017 - AUG 2017

# FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER INTERSHIP, JOBO

- Bringing mock-ups to life using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Angular.
- Implementing a mobile-first approach to existing website.

# **EDUCATION**

OCT 2014 – NOV 2018

BACHELOR'S DEGREE, NONG LAM UNIVERSITY